(Sheldon:)Is anyone else troubled
by the Spider-Man theme song?
(Leonard:)Why would it trouble you?
It's your third-favorite cartoon theme song.
(Sheldon:)It is, right behind,
"Do, do, do, do, do, Inspector Gadget."
(Sheldon:)And Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles.
Heroes in a half shell.
(Howard and Raj(together):)Turtle power.
(Sheldon:)However, the Spider-Man lyrics posit
that Spider-Man, Spider-Man...
(Sheldon:)...does whatever a spider can.
- Yeah, so?
(Sheldon:)I can think of many things
Spider-Man can't do that a spider can.
(Sheldon:)One, crawl in your ear and die.
(Sheldon:)Two, legally leave Guatemala
without a passport.
And three, have sex with a spider.
Can we change the subject?
Spiders give me the jeebie-jeebies.
It's "heebie-jeebies."
(Raj:)I know, but that sounds anti-Semitic.
(Raj:)I was thinking we could have
a little film festival tonight.